<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<PluginManifest Type="MacroPlugin" >
	<Name>Kurisu.VoiceOverTools</Name>
	<Title>Dialogue System Voice Over Helper</Title>
	<Version>1.0.11</Version>
	<MinimumArticyVersion>4.1</MinimumArticyVersion>
	<Developer>Christos Nasioutzikis</Developer>
	<Description>Voice-over asset helpers for dialogue projects. Rename VO files to a consistent {hexId}_{culture} scheme, clean up orphaned audio assets not referenced by any DialogueFragment, and strip non-primary translations + voice-over references in one pass. All commands include a dry-run preview.</Description>
	<ProjectUrl>https://github.com/kurisu-n/Articy-VoiceOver-Tools</ProjectUrl>
	<!--
	  optional manifest relative location of a 48x48 pixel image.
	  It is used in the plugin info dialog and is scaled down to
	  16x16 pixel if a GetIcon("$self") is not overridden or returns null.
	-->
	<IconFile>Resources\Icon.png</IconFile>
	<Tags>Voice-Over, Dialogue, Asset Management, Rename, Localization</Tags>
	<ReleaseNotes>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.0- Initial release version]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.1- Purge Voice Over and Translations Feature]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.2- Added "Clean Up Orphaned Voice-Overs" command with dry-run / delete-Articy / delete-Articy+disk options. Added dry-run preview window to Rename commands with per-entry status (already correct / will rename / display-only / target exists / source missing) and click-to-navigate. New Articy-style dark theme for all plugin windows. Bug fixes: RemoveVoiceOvers now resumes localization state handling on exception; silent-placeholder WAV is cleaned from disk after removal; removed dead helpers and unused imports.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.3- Plugin renamed from Kurisu.VoiceOverNamingScheme to Kurisu.VoiceOverTools (manifest Name, C# namespace, assembly, filenames). NOTE: this is a breaking rename — Articy treats it as a new plugin; uninstall the old one via Package Manager before installing 1.0.3. No behavioral changes.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.4- Added "Audit Voice-Overs" command (Global): scans every DialogueFragment and flags VO references that are missing for a language, corrupted (broken proxy / file missing on disk / 0-byte file), or overlapping (the same audio asset is shared by multiple distinct fragments). Read-only diagnostic with per-category filter toggles and click-to-navigate (Show Fragment / Show VO Asset).]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.5- Audit Voice-Overs filtering: hard-filter excludes fragments with no Speaker assigned (narration / stage directions don't get false-positive "Missing VO" entries). New per-character dropdown filter combines with the category toggles. Each row's header now includes the speaker name for at-a-glance scanning.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.6- Audit row redesign for transparency. Each entry now shows the navigator path of the fragment, the actual dialogue line in the audited language, and the issue detail in a structured 4-line layout with proper visual hierarchy (category icon + label, speaker, id+lang, path, quoted line, detail). Full ComboBox / ComboBoxItem template overrides so the character-filter dropdown is properly themed (was unreadable in dark mode previously).]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.7- Audit property + empty-line filtering. Each row now shows which text property the issue is for (.Text, .PreviewText, etc.) as a small monospaced badge in the header. New per-property toggle row dynamically built from the property names found in the audit (hidden when only one property type is present). New "Include empty lines" checkbox — hides rows whose dialogue text is blank by default (fragments not yet written), opt-in to include them.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.8- Audit by-path filter + UX polish. New "Path:" dropdown listing all path prefixes found in the audit (top-level folders, sub-folders, deeper) — picking a prefix narrows results to fragments under that branch. Works at any depth. All filters (categories / property / character / path / include-empty) consolidated into the summary panel for a cleaner hierarchy. Custom-templated CheckBox so the empty-lines toggle blends with the dark theme (was previously default-WPF-styled and out of place). Third grid row simplified to nav-buttons-only.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.9- Audit UX iteration. Empty-lines toggle promoted from a separate checkbox to a 4th category-style pill (off by default) so all primary filters share the same visual language. Character + Path filters moved back to the toolbar row alongside the Show buttons. Path picker rebuilt as a hierarchical ContextMenu — top-level folders cascade rightward into subfolders to any depth, with a "(this folder)" entry under each parent so you can filter at any intermediate level. Themed MenuItem / Separator / ContextMenu so the dropdown matches the dark palette.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.10- Audit dropdown stripe fix. ContextMenu is a logical-tree island in WPF — implicit MenuItem styles defined at the Window level were not propagating into it, so menu items rendered with the default Aero template (white-on-light icon column gutter on the left). Fixed by merging the theme dictionaries into the ContextMenu's own Resources and assigning the themed style explicitly to every MenuItem and Separator built in code.]]>
    <![CDATA[V1.0.11- Stripe fix v2 + Kurisu submenu. v1.0.10 didn't fully eliminate the white stripe in the path picker. v1.0.11 extracts the ControlTemplates as keyed resources and assigns them DIRECTLY on the ContextMenu and every MenuItem in code (Style propagation through Popup boundaries is unreliable in WPF). Also overrides Aero's role-keyed SubmenuItem/SubmenuHeader templates so the default never gets a chance to apply. All five plugin commands now prefixed "Kurisu/" so they group under a Kurisu submenu in the ribbon and right-click context menu (Articy menu-hierarchy convention).]]>
  </ReleaseNotes>
	<Properties>
		<!-- Is this plugin multi-user safe and properly checks claiming -->
		<Property Name="MultiUser" Value="false" />
		
		<!-- Can this plugin be used in single user projects -->
		<Property Name="SingleUser" Value="true" />

		<!-- Can this plugin be used in within API programs -->
		<Property Name="API" Value="false" />
	</Properties>
</PluginManifest>
